{
    "id": "3c70ee2701ad4304a0d11e00d01c0a68",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "At just 100 dollars, the laptop was a ............................",
            "description": "If something is a steal, it is a bargain.",
            "answers": [
                "steal",
                "deal",
                "robbery"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1735d4e8b78f430298c6b407701699b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you are on the lam, you are on the .............................",
            "description": "To be on the lam is to be on the run. ",
            "answers": [
                "prison",
                "run",
                "monastery"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f93a01556da4365ac946a6c37fc29a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He and his cousins are as thick as .................................",
            "description": "If two or more people are as thick as thieves, they are very close or friendly.",
            "answers": [
                "friends",
                "thieves",
                "robbers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18dd8e176fc1472b95731d91d5ed44cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you can sell a $100 product for $1000, you will make out like a .................................",
            "description": "To make out like a bandit is to make a large profit.",
            "answers": [
                "king",
                "bandit",
                "tycoon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "caaf8d0fdd964d5eaaac5ce0b7f5c413"
        },
        {
            "question": "Paying 10 dollars for 100 gram of cream is highway ......................................",
            "description": "Highway robbery means blatant and unfair overcharging.",
            "answers": [
                "theft",
                "burglary",
                "robbery"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a3c917075865468989925efeabb3bc45"
        },
        {
            "question": "When the organization discovered that he had served .................................. for theft, they chose not to hire him.",
            "description": "To serve time is to undergo a prison sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "time",
                "years",
                "months"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "27a9b898326044979166abd5b0f2545c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like crime thrillers. They are not my cup of ..............................",
            "description": "If something is your cup of tea, you like it.",
            "answers": [
                "juice",
                "tea",
                "coffee"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5ebf06f17af4a2b9206ba2cdd90cfc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She and her sister are like .................................... in a pod.",
            "description": "If people are like peas in a pod, they are very similar.",
            "answers": [
                "peas",
                "beans",
                "seeds"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6dae265f6df4936bbed0e9289a94389"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although he trained hard, he couldn't cut the ............................. as a gymnast.",
            "description": "To cut the mustard is to come up to expectations.",
            "answers": [
                "butter",
                "ginger",
                "mustard"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9161c362be73479ab1917d891cb24747"
        },
        {
            "question": "The heiress spends money like .................................",
            "description": "To spend money like water is to waste a lot of money. ",
            "answers": [
                "water",
                "wine",
                "juice"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4fdc22f673a842aab8fd8c819e033a3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Refugees have become a political hot ..................................",
            "description": "A hot potato is a controversial topic.",
            "answers": [
                "cake",
                "potato",
                "banana"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98def48227d54dbcbef096371c633830"
        },
        {
            "question": "His latest book is selling like hot .............................",
            "description": "If something is selling like hot cakes, it is selling well. ",
            "answers": [
                "cakes",
                "potatoes",
                "dogs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea8418648d4648e197854a9df5ad8a09"
        }
    ]
}